<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>The Buffaloner - Opinion</title><link href="https://buffaloner.me/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://buffaloner.me/feeds/opinion.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://buffaloner.me/</id><updated>2024-05-19T23:28:00-04:00</updated><subtitle>Anti Social Media Rebel</subtitle><entry><title>Anti Social Media Rebellion</title><link href="https://buffaloner.me/posts/2024/May/19/asmr/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-05-19T23:28:00-04:00</published><updated>2024-05-19T23:28:00-04:00</updated><author><name>The Buffaloner</name></author><id>tag:buffaloner.me,2024-05-19:/posts/2024/May/19/asmr/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;As I've been building &lt;a href="https://buffalonerbrand.com"&gt;Buffaloner Brand&lt;/a&gt; out, and using Social Media as a platform (albeit not currently promoting anything just yet) for marketing, I'm concerned about what info FB already has on me. All that I've seen in my feed are SEO optimized bots fishing for lonely men, hyper sexualized …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As I've been building &lt;a href="https://buffalonerbrand.com"&gt;Buffaloner Brand&lt;/a&gt; out, and using Social Media as a platform (albeit not currently promoting anything just yet) for marketing, I'm concerned about what info FB already has on me. All that I've seen in my feed are SEO optimized bots fishing for lonely men, hyper sexualized images of women whose busts and butts are ampilified, and 3rd world promoters shilling lessons on how to make money by charging for their course to get their 'secrets'...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm hoping that people don't bother wading through these news feeds anymore, or have figured out a way to only see people that matter to them personally. I know the only thing I want out of social media is knowing where to be @ IRL....and getting you to subscribe to my courses 😜&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Opinion"></category><category term="asmr"></category><category term="Social Media"></category></entry></feed>